Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company Agreements 5489
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company. Agreements, 1940-1966 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Agreement, 1953; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Between the Chesapeake and Ohio Railway (Chesapeake District) and Signal Department Employees represented by the Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America, covering Rates of Pay, Hours of Service, and Working Conditions
  - Item 12: Agreement, 1940; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Between the Chesapeake and Ohio Railway and Signal Employees represented by the Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America, covering Rates of Pay and Working Conditions
  - Item 13: Agreement, 1966; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Between the Chesapeake and Ohio Railway and All that Class of Clerical, Office, Station and Store Employees represented by the Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees
- Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company. Agreements, 1918-1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Working Conditions with Trainmen, 1963; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Chesapeake and Ohio Railway, Hocking Division. Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen
  - Item 2: Schedule of Wages and General Regulations for Engineers, Firemen and Hostlers, 1919; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 3)
    United States Railroad Administration, Director General of Railroads. Chesapeake and Ohio Railway; Chesapeake and Ohio Railway of Indiana. Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers; the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen.
  - Item 3: Rules and Regulations of the Operating Department, 1960; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: General Regulations for Clerical and Other Specified Employees, 1925; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Chesapeake and Ohio Railway; Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Clerks' Association
  - Item 5: Pass Rules, 1932; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Rules Governing the Use of Motor, Hand, Velocipede, Push, and Trailer Cars, 1938; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Safety Rules, 1968; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: List of Officers, Agents, Stations, Etc. No.82, 1948; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Issued by the Accounting Department, Chesapeake and Ohio Railway
  - Item 9: Schedule of Wages and General Regulations for Engineers, Firemen and Hostlers, 1918; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 3)
    United States Railroad Administration, W. G. McAdoo, Director General of Railroads. Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad; Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad of Indiana. Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers; the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen.
  - Item 10: Rules and Regulations Governing Working Conditions for Yardmasters, 1939; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Pere Marquette Railway; Switchmen's Union of North America
  - Item 11: Agreement, 1968; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Between the Baltimore and Ohio Railroad and All That Class of Employees Herein Specified Represented by the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees establishing Rules and Working Conditions
  - Item 12: The Standard Code of Block Signal and Interlocking Rules, 1938; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Association of American Railroads, Operations and Maintenance Department, Operating-Transportation Division
  - Item 13: General Regulations for Clerical and Other Specified Employees, 1931; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Rules Governing the Use of Motor, Hand, Velocipede, Push, and Trailer Cars, 1939; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company. Agreements and other pamphlets, 1938-1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A Yearbook of Railroad Information, 1943; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Eastern Railroad Presidents Conference, Committee on Public Relations
  - Item 2: Stations, Junctions and Connections, 1957; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Chesapeake and Ohio Railway. Accounting Department
  - Item 3: A Yearbook of Railroad Information, 1958; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Eastern Railroad Presidents Conference
  - Item 4: President's Board Views Firemen-Carrier Dispute: Recommends Basis for Settlement, 1952; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Discusses Wages and Working Rule Changes (4 copies)
  - Item 5: Chessie System Operating Rules, 1969; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Summary of Equipment, 1960; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Baltimore and Ohio Railroad; Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Chicago Terminal Railroad; Staten Island Rapid Transit Railway. Issued by Superintendent Car Service
  - Item 7: The Standard Code of Operating Rules, 1938; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Association of American Railroads, Operation and Maintenance Department, Operating - Transportation Division
  - Item 8: Code of Rules Governing the Condition Of, and Repairs To, Freight and Passenger Cars for the Interchange of Traffic, 1946; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Adopted by the Association of American Railroads, Operations and Maintenance Department, Mechanical Division. Supplement No. 1
  - Item 9: Yearbook of Railroad Information, 1968; Pamphlet (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Association of American Railroads